jlaforums.com 2009-05-12

# JLA FORUMS - Privacy Statement

**Privacy Statement**

Thank you for visiting the JLA FORUMS ("JLA") Internet web site located under the universal resource locator at: www.jlaforums.com ("Site"). We are providing this privacy policy in response to the growing concern over privacy on the Internet. 

**What we collect and how we use it.**  
JLA may ask you to provide personally identifiable information, such as your name, contact information, and e-mail address. In addition, we may ask you to provide your password, user identification number, and we may collect and log information regarding your internet protocol address, ISP, organization, referrer, search terms, os, browser type and screen resolution. When a visitor provides such information to us, we use it to: deliver requested goods, services or information; provide notices regarding goods or services you may purchase; verify your authority to enter the Site; and to improve the content and generally administer the Site along with any other stipulations mentioned in our Terms Of Service.

**My Profile Space (MPS) System**  
JLA also collects other profile data (when the user elects to submit this information) including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, education and occupation in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other. User Profile information including members' pictures and first names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the My Profile Space (MPS) social networking community. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join the JLA FORUMS and to add users to members' friends' networks. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's MPS personal network. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members unless the User has elected to enter their full name into the profile system. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, JLA allows users to search for other members using the variety of information fields that the MPS profile systems uses. Again, input of any of this information into the MPS system is purely voluntary and not required.

**Cookies**  
We use small text files called cookies to improve the overall Site experience. Cookies generally do not permit us to personally identify you. The use of cookies is now standard operating procedure for most Web sites.

**Third Party Advertising**  
Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to users by JLA or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by JLA and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Google DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on The JLA FORUMS

  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based upon your visit to this site and other sites on the internet

  * Users may opt out of of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**Disclosure**  
We will disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority or to prevent harm to yourself or others. In addition, we may transfer your personally identifiable information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which JLA participates or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of JLA's assets. Such successor entity shall be bound by the terms and conditions of this privacy policy.

**Links to Third Party Sites**  
This Site may be linked to other web sites on the Internet which are not under the control of or maintained by JLA. Such links do not constitute an endorsement by JLA of those other web sites, the content displayed therein, or the persons or entities associated therewith. You acknowledge that JLA is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and you agree that JLA is not responsible for the content of such sites. Your use of these other linked web sites is subject to the respective terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked sites.

**Security**  
JLA employs procedural and technological measures, consistent with the demands of customer service. Such measures are reasonably designed to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Where reasonably practical, JLA uses encryption, password protection, firewalls, internal restrictions and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information.

**Updating Your Information**  
If you wish to update your personally identifiable information please contact JLA at the address or e-mail address provided below.

**Policy Changes**  
JLA reserves the right to change this privacy policy, and will post any revisions on its website located at www.jlaforums.com We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this web site will be subject to the then-current privacy policy.

If you have questions or comments regarding JLA's privacy practices you can contact us at: JLA ENTERPRISES, 12100 Bedford Woods Drive, Suite 209 - Raleigh, NC 27614 or info@jlaenterprises.com. We will be sure to address your concerns.
